Finding Aid to the San Francisco Department of Public Health AIDS Office records SFH 4
San Francisco History Center, San Francisco Public Library
- Administrative Records, 1982-1994; Record Group 1; 22 Cubic Feet
  - Directors' Files, Subgroup 1; 13.1 Cubic Feet
    - Director's Office, AIDS Office, 1982-1994; Series 2
      - Assistant Director James Loyce, 1987-1993; Subseries 2.3
        - Troubleshooting Files, 1988-1992
          - AIDS Health Project / Bayview-Hunter's Point Foundation Cooperative Agreement, 1992 (Box 9, Folder 28)
          - AIDS Indigent Direct Services (A.I.D.S.) (Box 9, Folder 29-33)
          - Center for Positive Care (CPC) (Box 9, Folder 34)
          - Comunidad Unida en Respuesta AI Sida (CURAS) (Box 9, Folder 35)
            - Bylaws and 501(c) (3), 1988-1989 (Box 9, Folder 36)
            - Documents Requested by AIDS Office, December 1991 (Box 9, Folder 37)
            - Hispanic Headquarters Collaboration Dispute, September 1991 - April 1992 (Box 9, Folder 38)
            - Center for Positive Care Issues, December 1991 - September 1992 (Box 9, Folder 39)
            - Personnel Disputes, 1991-1992 (Box 9, Folder 40)
            - Carmen Chavez Dispute, November 1991 - August 1992 (Box 9, Folder 41)
            - Rodrigo Reyes Dispute, December 1991 - May 1992 (Box 9, Folder 42)
            - CURAS (Box 9, Folder 43, Box 10, Folder 22)
            - Tim Offutt-Rosmaria Zayas Dispute, January 1991 - March 1992 (Box 9, Folder 44)
            - Audit, August - October 1992 (Box 9, Folder 45)
            - Breach of Confidentiality Issue, April - May 1992 (Box 9, Folder 46)
            - Rescue Committee, July - December 1992 (Box 10, Folder 1)
            - Board of Directors Lists, July - October 1992 (Box 10, Folder 2)
            - Instituto Familiar De La Raza, November - December 1992 (Box 10, Folder 3)
            - Personnel & Fiscal Manuals, Program Services Protocol, Retreat Documentation, August - November 1992 (Box 10, Folder 4)
            - General Correspondence and Documents, 1991-1993 (Box 10, Folder 5-7)
      - Staff Meetings and Retreats, 1987-1992; Subseries 2.4; Boxes 10-11
        - Departmental AIDS Committee, 1987-1992 (Box 10, Folder 8-15)
        - Executive Staff Meetings, January 1987 - July 1992 (Box 10, Folder 16-21)
        - Senior Staff Meetings, December 1987 - September 1992 (Box 11, Folder 1)
        - Branch Chiefs Meetings, September 1988 - September 1992 (Box 11, Folder 2)
        - Quarterly Staff Meetings, May 1988 - April 1989 (Box 11, Folder 3)
        - Prevention Branch Meetings, March 1990 -March 1991 (Box 11, Folder 4)
        - AIDS Office Retreat, 1987-1992 (Box 11, Folder 5-10)
        - Operations Branch Retreat, 1989 (Box 11, Folder 11)
        - Operations Branch Staff Meeting Minutes, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 12)
        - Prevention Branch Retreat, 1989 (Box 11, Folder 13)
        - Health Services Branch Retreat, 1989 (Box 11, Folder 14)
        - Research Branch Retreat, 1989 (Box 11, Folder 15)
        - Surveillance Branch Retreat, 1989 (Box 11, Folder 16)
        - Branch Retreats, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 17)
      - Advisory Groups, Committees, Caucuses, and Councils, 1986-1993; Subseries 2.5
        Further divided into two subseries: 7.1: Internal; and 7.2: External.
        - Internal, 1986-1993; Boxes 11-12
          - Ad Hoc Infection Control Committee, October 1987 (Box 11, Folder 18)
          - Adolescent AIDS Task Force, November 1986 - October 1989 (Box 11, Folder 19)
          - AIDS Health Services Advisory Committee, April 1989 - June 1991 (Box 11, Folder 20)
          - AIDS Prevention Advisory Committee, 1989-1993 (Box 11, Folder 21-22)
          - AIDS Substance Abuse Task Force, November 1985 - September 1989 (Box 11, Folder 23)
          - Ambulatory Care Committee, December 1988, September 1989 (Box 11, Folder 24)
          - Community AIDS Advisory Committee, Janurary 1987 - January 1989 (Box 11, Folder 25)
          - Community Education Advisory Committee, April 1987 - October 1987 (Box 11, Folder 26)
          - Cultural Competency Advisory Committee, 1993 (Box 11, Folder 27)
          - Disciplinary Advisory Committee, October 1991-June 1992 (Box 11, Folder 28)
          - Journal Club, November 1987 - March 1990 (Box 11, Folder 29)
          - Lesbian & Bisexual Women's Survey Working Group, February - December 1992 (Box 11, Folder 30)
          - Lesbian, Gay & Bisexual People of Color Task Force, February - April 1990 (Box 11, Folder 31)
          - Mayor's AIDS Task Force, 1985-1991 (Box 11, Folder 32-34, Box 12, Folder 1)
          - Mayor's Fiscal Advisory Council, 1992 (Box 12, Folder 2)
          - Minority AIDS Advisory Committee, August 1986 - August 1990 (Box 12, Folder 3-8)
          - People of Color Advisory Committee, 1990-1992 (Box 12, Folder 9-11)
          - Parents' Support Group (AIDS Office Staff), 1990 (Box 12, Folder 12)
          - Pediatric/Perinatal AIDS Advisory Committee, September 1987 - January 1989 (Box 12, Folder 13)
          - Proposition 96 Committee, September 1988 - July 1989 (Box 12, Folder 14)
          - WEDGE Advisory Committee, 1988-1990 (Box 12, Folder 15)
          - Women's Health Committee, July - October 1989 (Box 12, Folder 16)
        - External, 1987-1992; Box 12
          - AIDS Epidemiology Consortium, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 17)
          - AIDS Policy Round Table (national), June 1991 - June 1992 (Box 12, Folder 18)
          - AIDS Research Coordinating Committee, December 1986 - November 1988 (Box 12, Folder 19)
          - Adolescent AIDS Network, February 1990 - May 1991 (Box 12, Folder 20)
          - Adult Day Health Planning Council, 1988-1989 (Box 12, Folder 21)
          - African American Men's Caucus, circa December 1990 (Box 12, Folder 22)
          - Children's AIDS Network, November 1989 (Box 12, Folder 23)
          - HIV Community-Based Plan Steering Committee, March 1990 - March 1991 (Box 12, Folder 24)
          - Latino AIDS Policy Group (Statewide), April 1991 - April 1992 (Box 12, Folder 25)
          - Substance Abuse and Mental Health in AIDS Center (SAMHA), 1986-1987 (Box 12, Folder 26-27)
      - Center for Positive Care (CPC), 1990-1993; Subseries 2.6; Boxes 12-13
        Biographical / Historical
        The Center for Positive Care began as the Early Intervention Resource Center (EIRC) in 1991 as a collaborative effort in which the AIDS Office contracted with community-based organizations (CBOs) to provide psychosocial services to people who are HIV positive. The site was administered by the AIDS Health Project, NTFAP, and Cal-Pep. (per Box 12, folder Planning Early Intervention, under CPC files).
        See also Boxes 52 (Contract Development) and 54-55 (Development files and reports)
        - Planning Early Intervention Resource Center, Center for Positive Care (Box 12, Folder 28)
        - Request For Proposal (Box 12, Folder 29)
        - Bidders Conference, March 1991 (Box 12, Folder 30)
        - Proposal Evaluation, Awards, and Notification (Box 12, Folder 31)
        - Provider Meetings, Memos, and 1991 Retreat (Box 12, Folder 32)
        - On-Site Providers (Box 12, Folder 33)
        - Management (Box 12, Folder 34)
        - Site Administration Subcontracts (Box 12, Folder 35)
        - Reorganization of CPC, Spring - Summer 1992 (Box 12, Folder 36)
        - Third Floor CPC Space (Box 12, Folder 37)
        - Service Providers Technical Review Panel – Notes (Box 12, Folder 38)
        - CARE Title III (Box 13, Folder 1)
        - CDC Budget, 1991 (Box 13, Folder 2)
        - CDC Grant, 1993 (Box 13, Folder 3)
        - CDC Grant Objectives and Quarterly Reports, 1990-1991 (Box 13, Folder 4)
        - Monitoring Notes (Box 13, Folder 5)
        - Monitoring Reports, 1992 (Box 13, Folder 6)
        - National Association of Black and White Men Together (NABWMT) / Early Advocacy and Care for HIV (EACH) Contract, FY 1990-1991 (Box 13, Folder 7)
        - NABWMT / EACH: Monitoring, 1990-1991 (Box 13, Folder 8)
        - NABWMT / EACH: Working Papers, 1990-1991 (Box 13, Folder 9)
        - CPC Closes (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Branch Files, 1985-1993; Subgroup 2
    Further divided into four series: Series 9: Health Services; Series 10: Fiscal Services; Series 11: Prevention; and Series 12: Surveillance. No Records from the Research Branch are held in this collection.
    - Health Services Branch, 1982-1992 and undated; Series 3
      FIles are arranged by topic; some topics are arranged alphabetically.
      - Public Health Service Hospital, 1987-1988 (Box 13, Folder 11-12)
      - Public Health Service Hospital Plan: Long-Term Care Project, 1988 (Box 13, Folder 13)
      - Skilled Nursing Facilities, 1987-1989 (Box 13, Folder 14)
      - Visiting Nurses Association, 1987-1988 (Box 13, Folder 15)
      - Statistics, undated (Box 13, Folder 16)
      - Substance Abuse Treatment at SFGH, 1987 (Box 13, Folder 17)
      - Sub-Acute, 1988 (Box 13, Folder 18)
      - Support Services (Legal) - Human Rights Commission, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 19)
      - AIDS Treatment and Prevention Centers (model), undated (Box 13, Folder 20)
      - Hospice of SF Program Review, 1987 (Box 13, Folder 21)
      - Research, 1987-1988 (Box 13, Folder 22)
      - Baker Places - Residential IV Drug User Treatment, 1988 (Box 13, Folder 23)
      - Shanti, 1988 (Box 13, Folder 24)
      - Research: West Bay Hospital Conference Inpatient AIDS Care, 1982-1987 (Box 13, Folder 25)
      - Women's and Children's Services, 1988 (Box 13, Folder 26)
      - AIDS Service Demo Grant, 1987-1988 (Box 13, Folder 27)
      - HSB Contract Summary, 1987-1988 (Box 13, Folder 28)
      - Survey of Unmet Needs, July 1991 (Box 13, Folder 29)
      - Women's Survey, September 1992 (Box 13, Folder 30)
      - HIV Infected Worker, 1990-1991 (Box 13, Folder 31)
      - HIV Infected Worker: SFGH Occupational Exposure Program, 1989-1990 (Box 13, Folder 32)
      - Mandatory Testing for Pregnant Women, 1990-1991 (Box 13, Folder 33)
      - Medical Use of Marijuana, 1992 (Box 13, Folder 34)
      - Partner Notification, 1989-1992 (Box 13, Folder 35)
      - Teen AIDS in Focus, 1991 (Box 13, Folder 36)
      - HIV Service Network Assessment (Martha Jennings Report), 1992 (Box 13, Folder 37)
      - AIDS Case Definition, 1991-1992 (Box 14, Folder 1-2)
      - AIDS Case Definition; Information from Outside Sources, undated (Box 14, Folder 3)
      - Health Services Workgroup Strategic Plan, 1989 (Box 14, Folder 4)
      - A.I.D.S. - Tenderloin Agency, undated (Box 14, Folder 5)
      - Community Research Alliance (CRA), undated (Box 14, Folder 6)
      - Clinical Trials - Statement by BCA, undated (Box 14, Folder 7)
      - Cross-Cultural Training Final Report, undated (Box 14, Folder 8)
      - Community Planning on HIV, undated (Box 14, Folder 9)
      - Community Forum AIDS Health Service, undated (Box 14, Folder 10)
      - Advocate Proposal - Minority Working Papers, 1989-1990 (Box 14, Folder 11)
      - AIDS Coordinating Committee (West Bay Hosp Cont) Position Paper, 1988 (Box 14, Folder 12)
      - AIDS Research Center, 1988 (Box 14, Folder 13)
      - AIDS Service Demo Projects, 1987 (Box 14, Folder 14)
      - Alternative Therapies, 1988 (Box 14, Folder 15)
      - Ambulatory Care, 1987-1988 (Box 14, Folder 16)
      - AZT; Availability to PWAs Needing It, 1986-1989 (Box 14, Folder 17)
      - COBRA, 1987-1988 (Box 14, Folder 18)
      - Coming Home Hospice, 1987-1988 (Box 14, Folder 19)
      - Day-Care, 1987-1988 (Box 14, Folder 20)
      - Food Programs, 1989 (Box 14, Folder 21)
      - Garden Sullivan, 1987 (Box 14, Folder 22)
      - General [Health Services Issues], 1987-1989 (Box 14, Folder 23)
      - Home Health Care, 1988 (Box 14, Folder 24)
      - Home Support Project, 1986-1987 (Box 14, Folder 25)
      - Human Rights Commission, 1988-1989 (Box 14, Folder 26)
      - Housing and Homeless, 1987-1989 (Box 14, Folder 27)
      - Hospitals, 1989 (Box 14, Folder 28)
      - Inpatient, 1987 (Box 14, Folder 29)
      - Interferon, 1987 (Box 14, Folder 30)
      - Long-term Care, 1988 (Box 14, Folder 31)
      - Medi-Cal Waiver, 1987-1989 (Box 14, Folder 32)
      - Mental Health Services, 1987-1988 (Box 14, Folder 33)
      - Minority: Latino, 1987-1988 (Box 14, Folder 34)
      - Outpatient Care, 1987-1988 (Box 14, Folder 35)
      - Planning, 1988 (Box 14, Folder 36)
      - Preventive Follow-Up Center, 1989 (Box 14, Folder 37)
      - Public Health Nursing, 1988 (Box 14, Folder 38)
    - Fiscal Services Branch, 1982-1993; Series 4
      Additional records of the Fiscal Services Branch are in Record Group 2: Contracts and Related Documents.
      The Fiscal Services Branch was previously known as the Operations Branch. (p.2 legacyprint finding aid).
      - Budgets, 1985-1993
        - Audits (Box 14, Folder 39)
        - AD VALOREM, 1988-1989 (Box 14, Folder 40)
        - AIDS Office, 1987-1988 (Box 14, Folder 41)
        - Minorities, 1988 (Box 14, Folder 42)
        - Administrative, 1989-1990 (Box 14, Folder 43)
        - Administrative City Supplemental, 1989-1990 (Box 14, Folder 44)
        - Administrative Consolidated, 1989-1990 (Box 14, Folder 45)
        - General Funds; Departmental, 1991-1993 (Box 14, Folder 46)
      - Maria Lemus Files, 1989-1991
        Lemus was the Chief of the Operations Branch (per Jan. 1991 organization chart).
        - Correspondence, Memos and Notes, 1989-1991 (Box 22, Folder 13-15)
        - Meeting Notes, 1990-1991 (Box 22, Folder 16)
        - Planning Meeting, 1990-1991 (Box 22, Folder 17)
      - Galen Leung Files, Subseries 4.1
        Leung was the AIDS Office Administration's Assistant Director for Planning (per Feb. 1991 AIDS Office Resource Directory).
      - Confidentiality (Box 22, Folder 18)
      - Requests for Supplemental Appropriation, 1982-1984 (Box 22, Folder 19)
      - Supplemental Appropriation Work Papers, October 1984 (Box 22, Folder 20)
      - Supplemental Appropriation Presentations, October 1984 (Box 22, Folder 28)
      - AIDS-Related Services Underwritten by SFDPH, July 1984 - June 1985 (Box 22, Folder 21)
      - AIDS Programs: Budgets Summary, 1985-1986 (Box 22, Folder 22)
      - Budget Work Papers, 1985-1986 (Box 22, Folder 23)
      - AAO Budget Presentations, 1985-1986 (Box 22, Folder 29)
      - Budget Modification, 1986-1987 (Box 22, Folder 24)
      - Budgets from Mayor and Board of Supervisors, 1986-1987 (Box 22, Folder 25)
      - Budgets to Mayor, 1986-1987 (Box 22, Folder 26)
      - Lists of Contracts Awarded by AIDS Office, undated (Box 22, Folder 27)
    - Prevention Branch, 1985-1993; Series 5
      - General, 1985-1989; Subseries 5.1
        Alphabetical by file heading.
        - Intramural Programs Section:
          - Community Substance Abuse Services (CSAS), 1988 (Box 14, Folder 47)
          - Education Ordinance, 1988 (Box 14, Folder 48)
          - Employee Education, 1989 (Box 14, Folder 49)
          - Family Health, 1988 (Box 14, Folder 50)
          - Forensics, 1988-1989 (Box 14, Folder 51)
          - Infection Control, 1987-1988 (Box 14, Folder 52)
          - Materials Review, 1988-1989 (Box 14, Folder 53)
          - San Francisco City Clinic (SFCC), 1988-1989 (Box 14, Folder 54)
          - School Programs, 1985-1989 (Box 14, Folder 55)
          - Tuberculosis (TB), 1989 (Box 14, Folder 56)
          - Youth Guidance Center (YGC), 1988-1989 (Box 14, Folder 57)
        - Intravenous Drug Users, 1986-1987 (Box 14, Folder 58)
        - Marriage License Bureau, 1987-1988 (Box 14, Folder 59)
        - Minorities - Asians, 1987 (Box 14, Folder 60)
        - Minorities - Kapuna West Inner-City Child / Family AIDS Network (KWIC-FAN), 1987 (Box 14, Folder 61)
        - Prevention in STD Patients, 1986-1987 (Box 14, Folder 62)
        - Proposal: Rowniak, Froner, and Biernacki, 1988 (Box 14, Folder 63)
        - Provider Education: Cross-Cultural Training, undated (Box 14, Folder 64)
        - Research- National Institute on Alcohol Abuse and Alcoholism (NIAAA) Center Grant, 1986-1988 (Box 14, Folder 65)
        - Review Committee for AIDS Educational Material, 1987 (Box 14, Folder 66)
        - Robert Wood Johnson Foundation (RWJF), 1985-1987 (Box 14, Folder 67)
        - RWJF Site Visit to AIDS Health Project, July 18, 1986 (Box 14, Folder 68)
        - Substance Abuse:
          - 1985-1989 (Box 15, Folder 1-2)
          - 18th Street Services (Box 15, Folder 3)
          - Hayes (Box 15, Folder 4)
          - NIDA Project (Box 15, Folder 5)
          - Research - School Education (Box 15, Folder 6)
          - Research - Sex Partners (Box 15, Folder 7)
          - School Education (Box 15, Folder 8-9)
          - School-based: Colleges (Box 14, Folder 10)
          - SB 1251 Funding (Box 15, Folder 11)
          - San Francisco AIDS Foundation (SFAF) (Box 15, Folder 12)
        - WEDGE (Box 15, Folder 13)
      - Early Intervention, 1986-1990; Subseries 5.2
        Alphabetical by topic or program.
        - Adolescents-out-of-school (Box 15, Folder 14)
        - Asian American Recovery Services (Box 15, Folder 15)
        - Clinic-CC Based (Box 15, Folder 16)
        - Correspondence; Pat Evans and Instituto, 1987-1988
          File listed on legacy finding aid but not found in the collection.
        - Correspondence; Early Intervention, 1989 (Box 15, Folder 17)
        - Department of Human Services (DHS) Block Grant, 1986-1987 (Box 15, Folder 18)
        - Education and Community-Based AIDS Prevention and Risk-Reduction (Box 15, Folder 19)
        - Education Program: American Indians, 1987 (Box 15, Folder 20)
        - Elderly, 1987-1988 (Box 15, Folder 21)
        - Epidemiology and Prevention Grant, 1986-1987 (Box 15, Folder 22)
        - Extramural Programs Section:
          - 18th St Services, 1988 (Box 15, Folder 23)
          - American Indian AIDS Institute, 1988-1989 (Box 15, Folder 24)
          - Bayview Hunters Point Foundation (BVHPF), 1988 (Box 15, Folder 25)
          - Health Outreach Team, 1988 (Box 15, Folder 26)
          - Instituto, 1987-1989 (Box 15, Folder 27)
          - Minorities: MIRA, 1988-1989 (Box 15, Folder 28)
          - Multicultural Training Resource Center (MTRC), 1988-1989 (Box 15, Folder 29)
          - National Campaign, 1988-1989 (Box 15, Folder 30)
          - San Francisco AIDS Foundation (SFAF), 1988-1989 (Box 15, Folder 31)
          - Tenderloin AIDS Network, 1988-1989 (Box 15, Folder 32)
          - WEDGE (Box 15, Folder 33)
        - Forensics, 1987-1989 (Box 15, Folder 34)
        - HIV Treatment Advocate Project (Box 15, Folder 35)
        - Instituto: Latino AIDS Project, 1988-1989 (Box 15, Folder 36)
        - Mob Against AIDS; Early Intervention, 1989 (Box 15, Folder 37)
        - Multicultural Training Resource Center (MTRC) Memos (Box 15, Folder 38)
        - Patient Advocates for Necessary Treatment (PANT), 1990 (Box 15, Folder 39)
        - Polaris - Cross Cultural Training (Box 15, Folder 40)
        - Prevention and Education: Hayes Report, 1988 (Box 15, Folder 41)
        - Relapse Prevention (Box 15, Folder 42)
        - Substance Abuse (Box 15, Folder 43)
        - Substance Abuse and AIDS - Latino Community (Box 15, Folder 44)
        - Women and AIDS (Box 15, Folder 45)
      - Tim Offutt Files A-C, 1990-1992; Subseries 5.3
        Offut was the Prevention Branch's Minority Initiatives Program Manager.
        - African American Prevention / Education RFP 144-91 (Box 15, Folder 46)
        - Agency / Clients Served (Box 15, Folder 47)
        - Agency Update "Galen [Leung] Report", 1991 (Box 15, Folder 48)
        - AIAI Monitoring (Box 15, Folder 49)
        - AIDS Volunteerism Proposal (Box 15, Folder 50)
        - AIDS Residential Programs (Box 15, Folder 51)
        - AIDS Educational Material Review (Box 15, Folder 52)
        - AIDS Indigent Direct Services (A.I.D.S.) (Box 15, Folder 53)
        - AIDS Institute for Gay & Bisexual Men of Color (Box 15, Folder 54)
        - Asian Pacific Islander; RFP (Box 15, Folder 55)
        - Asian AIDS Project Final Report, 1988-1989 (Box 15, Folder 56)
        - Asian Pacific Islander; New RFP Data (Box 15, Folder 57)
        - Asian Pacific Islander Consortium on AIDS (APICA) Monitoring (Box 15, Folder 58)
        - Assessment of Branch Accomplishments, 1989-1990 (Box 15, Folder 59)
        - AZT, State Funding (Box 15, Folder 60)
        - Bay View/Hunters Point (Box 15, Folder 61)
        - BVHP Monitoring, 1991 (Box 15, Folder 62)
        - BVHP Response to Monitoring Report (Box 15, Folder 63)
        - CARE MOU – SFGH (Box 15, Folder 64)
        - CDC: Prevention Grant Materials, 1991 (Box 16, Folder 1)
        - CDC; Cooperative Agreement for Youth (Box 16, Folder 2)
        - CDC; Cooperative Agreement, 1990 (Box 16, Folder 3)
        - CDC; Direct Funded Programs (Box 16, Folder 4)
        - CDC; Final Reports, 1991 (Box 16, Folder 5)
        - CDC; Health and Risk Education for Minority Initiatives (Box 16, Folder 6)
        - CDC; Health Education Risk Reduction, Minority Initiatives Budget, 1991 (Box 16, Folder 7)
        - CDC; Narrative (Box 16, Folder 8)
        - CDC; Objectives (Box 16, Folder 9)
        - CDC: Progress Report, January - March 1990 (Box 16, Folder 10)
        - CDC; Quarterly Reports (Box 16, Folder 11)
        - CDC; Site Visit-Asian AIDS Project (Box 16, Folder 12)
        - CDC; Site Visit, August 1991 (Box 16, Folder 13)
        - CDC; YES Proposal (Box 16, Folder 14)
        - Center for Health Policy Devel (Box 16, Folder 15)
        - Community Input Meetings (Box 16, Folder 16)
        - Contract Monitoring Protocol (Box 16, Folder 17)
        - Correlates of AIDS Risk Behaviors (Box 16, Folder 18)
        - Correspondence, January 1990 - December 1991 (Box 16, Folder 19-22)
        - Cultural Competency (Box 16, Folder 23)
        - Cultural Dimensions of the Pain Experience (Box 16, Folder 24)
        - Communidad Unida en Respuesta Al Sida (CURAS), 1990-1991 (Box 16, Folder 25)
        - CURAS; Evaluation, 1991 (Box 16, Folder 26)
        - CURAS; Reports, 1991 (Box 16, Folder 27)
      - Pat Evans Files, 1987-1989; Subseries 5.4
        Evans was Chief, Senior Physician Specialist (per 1988 org chart)
        - Correspondence, Notes, Misc., 1987-1989 (Box 16, Folder 28)
        - Correspondence with Instituto Familiar de la Raza, 1987-1988 (Box 16, Folder 29)
        - Complaint folder (Box 16, Folder 30)
        - Video For ATS, 1987 (Box 16, Folder 31)
        - Bibliography, AIDS Office, circa 1988 (Box 16, Folder 32)
        - Conference for Black Clergy On AIDS, December 1987 (Box 16, Folder 33)
        - Condoms, 1987 (Box 16, Folder 34)
        - WEDGE (Box 16, Folder 35)
        - Chapter on AIDS from STD Clinic Training Manual, 1988 (Box 16, Folder 36)
        - Review of Educational Materials - Procedures (Box 16, Folder 37)
      - Contract Monitoring, 1987-1993; Subseries 5.5
        - SF AIDS Foundation; Monitoring, 1987, 1989, 1991 (Box 16, Folder 38-40)
        - Urban Health Study; Monitoring, 1991 (Box 16, Folder 41)
        - Tenderloin AIDS Network; Program Reports, 1989-1990, 1990-1993 (Box 17, Folder 1-2)
        - Tenderloin AIDS Network; Correspondence, 1991-1993 (Box 17, Folder 3)
        - AIDS Homecare and Hospice Program; Hospice Monitoring, 1986-1987 (Box 17, Folder 4)
        - Forensic AIDS Project; Monitoring, 1989-1990 (Box 17, Folder 5)
      - WEDGE, 1987-1990; Subseries 5.6
        - AIDS Education in SF Schools (Box 17, Folder 6)
        - Teaching Kids About STDs (Box 17, Folder 7)
        - AIDS Videos WEDGE Video Project: "Teen AIDS In Focus", 1988 (Box 17, Folder 8)
        - Memorandum of Understanding, (MOU), 1988 (Box 17, Folder 9)
        - SOMBA (First Fiscal Agent) Correspondence (Box 17, Folder 10)
        - Correspondence, 1988-1990 (Box 17, Folder 11)